http://hardware.idn-inc.com/privacy/

Web Store Log-In
Select Language
Home  >  Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We value you as a customer and take your personal privacy seriously. The following describes our information practices for this website, idn-inc.com
Our Privacy Principles
•  We do not sell customer information.
•  We do not provide customer information to persons or organizations outside IDN, Inc. for their own marketing purposes.
Information We Collect
We collect and use information we believe is necessary to administer our business, to advise you about our products and promotions, and to provide you with customer service. We may collect and maintain customer information needed for these purposes, such as name, address, telephone number, and email address. We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily submit such information to us.
Other Sites
This site may contain links to other sites that are not owned, maintained, operated, or endorsed by or for IDN, Inc. and are not subject to the same Privacy Policy. IDN, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
Revisions
We may from time to time revise our privacy policy by updating this posting. Amendments to our privacy policy will be effective when posted. You should periodically visit this page to review the then current policy so you are aware of any such revisions. By continuing to use the Site after we post any changes, you agree to the terms of the updated policy. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact us through our Request Information page.
Translate »
Live Chat
We're not around right now. But you can send us an email and we'll get back to you, asap.
Your name *:
E-mail *:
Got a question? *:
Send
Questions, issues or concerns? I'd love to help you!
End chat
Click ENTER to chat
